Guide to the History of Education Society collection, 1960-2013 MS2341
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Governance and Society records, 1960-2006; Series 2
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor McClelland, December 17, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Mehafly, 1981-1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Miller Phillipson, Hanham, 1981-1985; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson & Professor Mungazi, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Palmer, March 13, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Perko and Jones, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Powell, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Pratt, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Prentice, December, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Provenzo, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Rashid, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Ringer, February 28, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Ringer, Day, 1979, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Schlafly, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Schneer, November 11, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Schutte and Harvey and Kingdon, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Scott, May 4, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Scott, Mitchell, Smith, 1980-1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Shawen, February, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Sheehan, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Skopp, April 1, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Strickland, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Strickland, 1981; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Sutherland, Burstyn, 1982; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Talbott, November 13, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Talbott, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Talbott, Ringer, November 13, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Thompson, March 21, 1985; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Underwood, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Vogel, 1980; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Robert Wagoner, 1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Warren, 1979; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Weiss, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Westbrook, Mr. Mattingly, 1976-1983; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Williams, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Professor Yannicopoulos, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and R. Cooper, 1984; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence with Paul H. Mattingly, 1974; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Professor Roger Phelps, August 1, 1974; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Richard Robinger, and W. Donald Burton, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Robert B. Everhart, September, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Arnold Cooper, and Robert F. Engs, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Robin Hume, 1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Robert McClintock, and John H. Geerken, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Robert T. Blackburn, Jurgen Herbst, 1982-1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Robert T. Georgia, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Rollin J. Watson, 1983; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Roman Rome, and Edward Stevens, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Sandra H.P., and William Keylor, 1979-1980; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Sister Anita Taylor, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Steven Brent, 1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Susan B. Yutzey, 1984; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Thomas Lacqueur, September 4, 1979; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and University of Chicago Press, 1983-1984; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and Vogt, March 30, 1984; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and William B. Rutherford, September 23, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, William "Bill" Reese, and Mark H. Van Pelt, 1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and William F. Cox, 1984-1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and William R. Lee, 1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson and William R. Lee, 1983; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Robin Berson, Young, Leith, Bailey, Beyerchen, 1983-1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Robin G.S. Kealy and Professor Mattingly, January, 1979; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Roderic A. Camp and Paul Mattingly, March 21, 1978; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Roger D. Long and Paul H. Mattingly with attachment, September 14, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Ron Goodenow and Paul, May 30, 1984; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Ron Goodenow and Professor McLachlan, 1984; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence with Ronald D. Cohen, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Ronald Cohen and Paul Mattingly, 1972-1974; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Ronald Cohen and Sol Cohen, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Ronald D. Cohen and Robin, January 20, 1983; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Ronald E. Butchart and Robin K. Berson, September 22, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Ronald Goodenow and Wayne J. Urban, February 12, 1980; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Ronald K. Goodenow and Douglas Sloan, October 15, 1984; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Samuel Haber, Paul H. Mattingly, and Clarence J. Karier, 1977; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Sanford Elwitt and Robin Berson, August 10, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Secretary and Mrs. Mariam C. Hausman, October 9, 1974; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence with Secretary to Division of Historical and Philosophic Foundations, August 23, 1973; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Advertising Manager, March 11, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Blackwells, March 12, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Change Magazine, November 6, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Charles R. Bailey, October 21, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Memorandum to Dean Lou Kleinman, January 7, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Memorandum to Dean Lou Kleinman, January 24, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Memorandum to Dean Lou Kleinman, June 3, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Miss Hester M. Hollaar, January 22, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Miss Naomi J. Collett, August 13, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mr. Harry Kelly, February 12, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mr. J.C. B. Bigala, December 5, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mr. John Florer, February 7, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mr. John H. Milor, December 3, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mr. Joseph M. McCarthy, January 29, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mr. Milton G. Simms, March 12, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mr. W.A. Bruneau, January 27, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mrs. Edith Ratshin, May 8, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mrs. Florence Lemons, February 12, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mrs. Irene Q. Brown, April 11, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mrs. J.T. Wilbur, January 13, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mrs. M. Vazir, January 31, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mrs. Marion Korllos, January 24, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mrs. Murray Chastain, January 17, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Mrs. Robert L. Teweles, January 13, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Alfred H. Jones, January 6, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Arnold Anderson, June 16, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Berenice Fisher, March 26, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Bruce White, February 7, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Burton Krasenbaum, January 28, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Charles D. Biebel, October 30, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Clarence Karier, August 19, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Daniel Dorotich, January 17, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor David Tyack, February 19, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Franklin Parker, March 7, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor George V. Guy, May 22, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Gilbert Noble, January 16, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Harold Dunkel, May 12, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Hyman Kuritz, March 3, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Hyman Kuritz, January 30, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Hyman Kuritz, October 13, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Jerome L. Rodnitzky, February 7, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Joel T. Rosenthal, October 1, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Keith W. Olson, October 22, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Kenneth Medlin, January 6, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Lloyd P. Jorgenson, April 26, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Melvin Urofsky, April 21, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence between Paul Mattingly and Professor Melvin Urofsky, April 22, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Robert S. Patterson, March, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Ronald L. Gougher, September 11, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor Sterling Fishman, February 12, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor William B. Lauderdale, December 10, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor William Brickman, December 9, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor William E. Segall, January 17, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor William K. Medlin, April 29, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and Professor William K. Medlin, August 19, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence between Secretary to History of Education Quarterly and The Library, January 20, 1969; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence between Selma Berrol and David Ment, July 31, 1989; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence between Selma Berrol and Joel Perlman, October, 1989; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence between Sheldon Rothblatt and James McLachlan, January 10, 1985; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence between Sheldon Rothblatt and Joan Burstyn, August 7, 1986; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence between Sidney Hertzberg and Paul H. Mattingly, September 30, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence between Sidney Holloway and Paul Mattingly, 1971, 1973; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Barbara Finkelstein, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Carl Kaestle, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Carl Kaestle, March, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Donald Warren, April, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and E.V. Johanningmeier, October 29, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence with Sol Cohen [on] Evaluation of the Editorship of the History of Education Quarterly, May 12, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Condliffe, October, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Jurgen Herbst, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Jurgen Herbst, September 17, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Kathryn M. Moore, April 27, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Kathryn Moore, April 27, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Marvin Lazerson, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Marvin/Ron, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen to Members of History of Education Society Newsletter Committee, November 12, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Murray S. Shereshewsky, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Neil Sutherland, November 4, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence between Sol Cohen and Paul Mattingly, April 15, 1982; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence between Alan H. Jane and Marvin Lazerson, February 14, 1984; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence between Allan S. Horlick and Doubleday & Company, October 14, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence between B. Edward McClellan and Judson C. Faurer, February 17, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence between B. Edward McClellan and Mr. Jay Thomas Horbelt, June 11, 1987; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Bernice Fisher, 1982; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence between Bertram H. Davis and Association Member, December 30, 1971; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence between Bob Belding and Dr. Charles Burgress, January 24, 1972; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence between Calvin Kytle and Robin Berson w/ Enclosure, 1981; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence between Charles Burgress and Glen Hass, July 2, 1971; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence between D.K. De Jager and Paul H. Mattingly, May 22, 1979; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence between David B. Tyack and Robert E. Belding, November 10, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence between David Tyack and History of Education Society Board, 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence between David Madsen and Professor Ezri Atzmon, December 2, 1971; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence between Dr. David Brock and Entire Faculty, October 23, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence between Douglas Sloan and Donald Wilson, May 5, 1983; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between E. Patricia Tsurumi, Robin Berson, and Paul H. Mattingly, 1979; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and Allen Wieder, May 19, 1987; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and Bloomingon, Undated; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and Eugene F. Provenzo, September 23, 1987; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and Jennings Wagoner, January 18, 1984; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and John Sommerville, Undated; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and Lynn D. Gordon, Undated; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and R. L. Schnell, Undated; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence between Edward McClellan and Robert L. Church, Undated; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence between Edwin H. Goldenstein and Dr. David Tyack, May 21, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence between Erwin V. Johanningmeier and Jennings L. Wagoner, 1984; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence between Everett D. Cantz and Dr. Ezri Atzmon, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and American Association of University Professors, March 13, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Ann Gallagher, June 2, 1967; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Ann Keppel, 1967; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Charles Burgess, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Mertens and Company, June 15, 1967; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Dean Daniel E. Griffiths, March 3, 1970; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Dean W. Ronald MacDonald, 1967; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Dr. Roberta Sayles, April 1, 1971; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and International University Booksellers, August 24, 1967; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Mr. Gary J. Gershwind, October 10, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Professor A.H. Miller, October 9, 1968; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Professors John Calam, February 1, 1972; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Professor Patricia Graham, October, 1972; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Professor R.S. Patterson, December 4, 1968; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Professor Robert S. Paterson, 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence between Ezri Atzmon and Professor Saul Sack, February 1, 1972; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence between Father Michael Perko and Jennings Wagoner, June 27, 1984; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence between Fisher and Berenice, January 7, 1969; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence between Francis L. Broderick and Henry J. Perkinson, 1967; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 46)